<resources>

    <!-- total (1) -->
    <string name="app_name">DoctorCom</string>
    <string name="license_title">END USER LICENSE AGREEMENT</string>
    <string name="license_content">	   &lt;p>&lt;b>This End User License Agreement (“Agreement”) is a binding legal contract between you (either an individual or a legal entity) and DoctorCom, Inc. (“DoctorCom”).  By downloading, installing, accessing or using the accompanying software (the “Application”) you will be bound by the terms of this Agreement.  If you do not agree to the terms of this Agreement, DoctorCom is not willing to grant you any right to use or access the Application to you.  In such event, you may not download, install, access, use or copy the Application.&lt;/b> &lt;/p> 
&lt;p>The Application is licensed to you, not sold. Except for the limited license granted in this Agreement, DoctorCom and its licensors retain all right, title and interest in the Application and all proprietary rights in the Application, including copyrights, patents, trademarks and trade secret rights. &lt;/p> 
&lt;p>&lt;b>1. Grant of License. &lt;/b> DoctorCom grants you a revocable, nontransferable (except as provided below), nonexclusive license to use the object code version of the Application for use on your mobile device.&lt;/p>  
&lt;p>&lt;b>2. Limitations On License.&lt;/b>  The license granted to you in this Agreement is restricted as follows: &lt;/p> 
&lt;p>&lt;b>•	Limitations on Copying and Distribution.&lt;/b>  You may not copy or distribute the Application except to the extent that copying is necessary to use the Application for purposes set forth herein. &lt;/p> 
&lt;p>&lt;b>•	Limitations on Reverse Engineering and Modification.&lt;/b>  You may not reverse engineer, decompile, disassemble, modify or create works derivative of the Application. &lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;b>•	Sublicense, Rental and Third Party Use. &lt;/b> You may not assign, sublicense, rent, timeshare, loan, lease or otherwise transfer the Application, or directly or indirectly permit any third party to use or copy the Application. &lt;/p>   
&lt;p>&lt;b>•	Proprietary Notices. &lt;/b> You may not remove any proprietary notices (e.g., copyright and trademark notices) from the Application. &lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;b>•	Use in Accordance with Documentation.&lt;/b>  All use of the Application must be in accordance with its then current documentation.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;b>•	Compliance with Applicable Law.&lt;/b> You are solely responsible for ensuring your use of the Application is in compliance with all applicable foreign, federal, state and local laws, and rules and regulations.  &lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;b>3. Account Set-Up. &lt;/b> You agree to: (a) provide true, accurate, current, and complete information when registering to use the Application and establishing your account (“Registration Information”) and (b) maintain and promptly update the Registration Information to keep it true, accurate, current, and complete. If you provide any information that is untrue, inaccurate, not current, or incomplete, or DoctorCom has reasonable grounds to suspect that such information is untrue, inaccurate, not current, or incomplete, DoctorCom may suspend or terminate your account. You are entirely responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of any passwords and any usage and activities that occur in connection with your account. You agree not to allow others to access your account or utilize your password.  &lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;b>4. Fees. &lt;/b> You agree to pay the license fees for the rights as set forth in the separate Order Form or similar ordering document provided by DoctorCom describing the license fees and any other fees owed by you. All fees are non-cancellable and non-refundable.&lt;/p> 
&lt;p>&lt;b>5. Termination.&lt;/b>  This license will automatically terminate in the event you breach any of its terms.  In the event of a claim of intellectual property infringement by any third party relating to the Application, DoctorCom may immediately terminate this Agreement.   &lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;b>6. Privacy. &lt;/b> DoctorCom recognizes the importance of respecting the privacy of those who visit its websites. The DoctorCom Privacy Policy  provides a description of how DoctorCom collects, uses, shares and protects personal information on its website, as well as the choices and access rights you have in regards to such personal information. &lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;b>7. Website Terms of Use. &lt;/b> Your use of the DoctorCom website and services available through the website are governed by DoctorCom’s Website Terms of Use.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;b>8. Location-Enabled Features. &lt;/b> Certain location-enabled functionality made available in the Application is provided by Yahoo, Inc. (“Yahoo”).  Your use of that functionality is subject to Yahoo’s terms and conditions, available at  http://info.yahoo.com/privacy/us/yahoo/location/ (as updated from time to time).  You must exercise your own judgment as to the adequacy and appropriatenesavailables of the information.  All location-based information is provided entirely “as-is,” without warranties of any kind.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;b>9. Warranty Disclaimer. &lt;/b> THE APPLICATION IS PROVIDED ON AN “AS AVAILABLE,” “AS IS” BASIS.  TO THE MAXIMUM EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW, DOCTORCOM AND ITS LICENSORS DISCLAIM ALL WARRANTIES WITH RESPECT TO THE APPLICATION, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF NON-INFRINGEMENT, TITLE, MERCHANTABILITY, QUITE ENJOYMENT, QUALITY OF INFORMATION, AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  DOCTORCOM DOES NOT WARRANT THAT THE APPLICATION WILL MEET YOUR REQUIREMENTS, OR THAT THE OPERATION OF THE APPLICATION WILL BE UNINTERRUPTED OR ERROR-FREE, OR THAT DEFECTS IN THE APPLICATION WILL BE CORRECTED.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>YOUR WIRELESS CARRIER, THE MANUFACTURER AND RETAILER OF YOUR MOBILE DEVICE, THE DEVELOPER OF THE OPERATING SYSTEM FOR YOUR MOBILE DEVICE, AND THE OPERATOR OF ANY APPLICATION STORE OR SIMILAR SERVICE THROUGH WHICH YOU OBTAIN THE APPLICATION (COLLECTIVELY, THE “THIRD PARTIES”) ARE NOT PARTIES TO THIS AGREEMENT AND THEY DO NOT OWN AND ARE NOT RESPONSIBLE FOR THE APPLICATION.  YOU AGREE (I) THE THIRD PARTIES DISCLAIM ALL WARRANTIES, EXPRESS AND IMPLIED, WITH RESPECT TO THE APPLICATION, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF NON-INFRINGEMENT, TITLE, MERCHANTABILITY, QUIET ENJOYMENT, QUALITY OF INFORMATION, AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE; (II) IN NO EVENT WILL THE THIRD PARTIES BE LIABLE TO YOU OR ANY THIRD PARTY FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, PUNITIVE, EXEMPLARY, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES (WHETHER IN CONTRACT, TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE), OR OTHERWISE) ARISING OUT OF THIS AGREEMENT OR THE APPLICATION, EVEN IF THEY HAVE BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES OR LOSSES; (III) IN ANY EVENT, THE MAXIMUM LIABILITY OF ANY THIRD PARTY FOR ALL CLAIMS (WHETHER IN CONTRACT, TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE), OR OTHERWISE) OF EVERY KIND WILL IN NOT EXCEED FIVE DOLLARS ($5.00); AND (IV) YOU WAIVE ANY AND ALL CLAIMS, NOW KNOWN OR LATER DISCOVERED, THAT YOU MAY HAVE AGAINST THE THIRD PARTIES ARISING OUT OF THE APPLICATION AND THIS AGREEMENT.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;b>10. Medical Disclaimer&lt;/b> Any content transferred by, or included on, the Application, including without limitation, text, copy, audio, video, photographs, illustrations, graphics and other visuals, or any medical information or records is for informational purposes only and does not constitute professional medical advice, diagnosis, treatment or recommendations of any kind and should not be used to make final or determinative medical decisions or treatment decisions. You should always review and analyze all original medical records or test information prior to providing professional medical treatment. Reliance on any information appearing on or transferred to the Application, whether provided by the Company, its content provides, its clients, or others, is solely at your own risk. &lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;b>11. Limitation Of Liability. &lt;/b> TO THE MAXIMUM EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW, IN NO EVENT WILL DOCTORCOM OR ITS SUPPLIERS/LICENSORS BE LIABLE TO YOU OR ANY THIRD PARTY FOR ANY DIRECT, SPECIAL, INCIDENTAL, CONSEQUENTIAL, PUNITIVE, OR INDIRECT DAMAGES (WHETHER IN CONTRACT, TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE), OR OTHERWISE), WHICH INCLUDE, WITHOUT LIMITATION, DAMAGES FOR PERSONAL INJURY, LOST PROFITS, LOST DATA AND BUSINESS INTERRUPTION, ARISING OUT OF THE USE OR INABILITY TO USE THE APPLICATION, EVEN IF DOCTORCOM HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES.  IN ANY CASE, THE ENTIRE LIABILITY OF DOCTORCOM AND ITS SUPPLIERS/LICENSORS UNDER THIS AGREEMENT FOR ALL DAMAGES, LOSSES, AND CAUSES OF ACTION (WHETHER IN CONTRACT, TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE), OR OTHERWISE) IS LIMITED TO THE PAID BY YOU, IF ANY, FOR THE APPLICATION.  &lt;/p>
&lt;p>Some states do not allow the exclusion of incidental or consequential damages, or the limitation on how long an implied warranty lasts, so some of the above may not apply to you.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;b>12. General. &lt;/b>This Agreement will be construed, interpreted, and performed exclusively according to the laws of the State of California, United States of America, without giving effect to any principles of conflicts of law.  Any action at law or in equity arising out of or directly or indirectly relating to this Agreement may be instituted only in the Federal or state courts located in Santa Clara, California. You and DoctorCom consent and submit to the personal jurisdiction of those courts for the purposes of any action related to this Agreement, and to extra-territorial service of process. You agree that regardless of any statute or law to the contrary, any claim or cause of action that you may have arising out of or related to this Agreement must be filed within one (1) year after the claim or cause of action arose.  This Agreement constitutes the entire understanding and agreement between DoctorCom and you with respect to the transactions contemplated in this Agreement and supersedes all prior or contemporaneous oral or written communications with respect to the subject matter of this Agreement, all of which are merged in this Agreement.  This Agreement shall not be modified, amended or in any way altered except by an instrument in writing signed by authorized representatives of both parties.  In the event any provision of this Agreement is found invalid or unenforceable pursuant to judicial decree, the remainder of this Agreement will remain valid and enforceable according to its terms.  Any failure by DoctorCom to strictly enforce any provision of this Agreement will not operate as a waiver of that provision or any subsequent breach of that provision.  The disclaimers and limitations of liability will survive any termination or expiration of this Agreement.  This Agreement may be accepted in electronic form (e.g., by an electronic or other means of demonstrating assent) and your acceptance will be deemed binding between you and DoctorCom. Neither you nor DoctorCom will contest the validity or enforceability of this Agreement, including under any applicable statute of frauds, because it was accepted or signed in electronic form. Electronically maintained records when produced in hard copy form shall constitute business records and shall have the same validity as any other generally recognized business records.  IT IS EXPRESSLY UNDERSTOOD AND AGREED THAT IN THE EVENT ANY REMEDY HEREUNDER IS DETERMINED TO HAVE FAILED OF ITS ESSENTIAL PURPOSE, ALL LIMITATIONS OF LIABILITY AND EXCLUSIONS OF DAMAGES WILL REMAIN IN EFFECT.&lt;/p>  </string>
    <string name="agree">Zustimmen</string>
    <string name="disagree">Ablehnen</string>
    <string name="loading">Wird geladen&#8230;</string>
    <string name="messages">Nachrichten</string>
    <string name="doctors">Ärzte</string>
    <string name="settings">Einstellungen</string>
    <string name="tasks">Aufgaben</string>
    <string name="invitations">Einladungen</string>
    <string name="user_name">Benutzername:</string>
    <string name="password">Kennwort:</string>
    <string name="login">Login</string>
    <string name="ok">OK</string>
    <string name="cancel">Abbrechen</string>
    <string name="network_not_available">{\&quot;errno\&quot;: \&quot;-1\&quot;, \&quot;descr\&quot;: \&quot;Keine Internetverbindung&#8230;!\&quot;}</string>
    <string name="cannot_be_empty">&lt;font color=blue&gt;Eingabe erforderlich!&lt;/font&gt;</string>
    <string name="field_invalid">&lt;font color=blue&gt;Eingabe ist ungültig!&lt;/font&gt;</string>
    <string name="process_text">Daten werden verarbeitet&#8230;</string>
    <string name="system_request_error">Anfrage gescheitert, bitte erneut versuchen!</string>
    <string name="no_data">Datenfehler. </string>
    <string name="sent_time">Sendezeit:</string>
    <string name="load_more">Mehr anzeigen &#8230;</string>
    <string name="quit">Beenden</string>
    <string name="logout">Ausloggen</string>
    <string name="refresh">Aktualisieren</string>
    <string name="about_doctorcom">Über DoctorCom</string>
    <string name="version_name_colon">Version: </string>
    <string name="about">Über</string>
    <string name="call">Anrufen</string>
    <string name="more">Mehr</string>
    <string name="received">Empfangen</string>
    <string name="back">Zurück</string>
    <string name="sent">Gesendet</string>
    <string name="of">von</string>
    <string name="show_detail">Zeige Details</string>
    <string name="hide_detail">Verberge Details</string>
    <string name="at">Am:</string>
    <string name="reply">Antworten</string>
    <string name="forward">Weiterleiten</string>
    <string name="follow_up">Folgemaßnahme</string>
    <string name="view_attachments">Zeige Anhänge</string>
    <string name="from">Von:</string>
    <string name="to">An:</string>
    <string name="cc">Cc:</string>
    <string name="no_subject">&lt;Kein Betreff&gt;</string>
    <string name="no_content">&lt;Kein Inhalt&gt;</string>
    <string name="accept">Annehmen</string>
    <string name="decline">Ablehnen</string>
    <string name="referring_physician">Überweisender Arzt:</string>
    <string name="physician_phone">Rufnummer des Arztes:</string>
    <string name="office_phone">Büronummer:</string>
    <string name="practice_name">Praxisname:</string>
    <string name="city">Stadt:</string>
    <string name="state">Bundesland:</string>
    <string name="address">Adresse:</string>
    <string name="patient_name">Patientenname:</string>
    <string name="gender">Geschlecht:</string>
    <string name="date_of_birth">Geburtsdatum:</string>
    <string name="phone">Rufnummer:</string>
    <string name="alternative_phone">Weitere Rufnummer:</string>
    <string name="refer_mrn">MRN:</string>
    <string name="refer_ssn">SSN:</string>
    <string name="insurance">Name der Krankenversicherung:</string>
    <string name="insurance_id">Versichertennummer:</string>
    <string name="primary_insurance">Name der Zusatzversicherung:</string>
    <string name="primary_insurance_id">Versicherungsnummer:</string>
    <string name="reason_of_refer">Grund der Überweisung:</string>
    <string name="attachments">Anhänge</string>
    <string name="speaker_on">Lautsprecheer An</string>
    <string name="speaker_off">Lautsprecher Stumm</string>
    <string name="attachments_cannot_load">Anhänge können nicht geladen werden, bitte erneut versuchen.</string>
    <string name="load_attchment">Anhang wird geladen, bitte warten.</string>
    <string name="connecting">Wird verbunden</string>
    <string name="encrypt">Wird verschlüsselt</string>
    <string name="done">Fertig</string>
    <string name="progress">Fortschritt:</string>
    <string name="download_file_fail_warning">Download der Datei gescheitert </string>    
    <string name="refer_accept_success">Überweisung erfolgreich angenommen!</string>
    <string name="refer_decline_success">Überweisung abgelehnt!</string>
    <string name="decline_reason">Grund der Ablehnnung: (Optional)</string>
    <string name="yes">Ja</string>
    <string name="no">Nein</string>
    <string name="delete_message_warning">Möchten Sie diese Nachricht wirklich löschen?</string>
    <string name="message_deleting">Nachricht wird gelöscht&#8230;</string>
    <string name="delete_successfully">Löschen erfolgreich!</string>
    <string name="call_back_title">Rückruf Nummer: </string>
    <string name="call_back">Rückruf</string>
    <string name="close">Schließen</string>
    <string name="send">Senden</string>
    <string name="new_message">Neue Nachricht</string>
    <string name="subject">Betreff:</string>
    <string name="system">System</string>
    <string name="exit_affirm">Bitte erneut drücken, um DoctorCom zu beenden.</string>
    <string name="error_occur">Fehler aufgetreten</string>
    <string name="number_enter_warning">Mind. 10 Ziffern sind einzugeben!</string>
    <string name="action_successed">Erfolgreich!</string>
    <string name="page_title">Rückrufnummer</string>
    <string name="leave_your_number_here">hier Ihre Rufnummer eingeben</string>
    <string name="take_photo">Foto aufnehmen</string>
    <string name="sdcard_unavailable">Keine SD-Card gefunden.</string>
    <string name="write_sdcard_fail">Schreiben auf SD-Card gescheitert, bitte überprüfen und erneut versuchen!</string>
    <string name="search">Suche</string>
    <string name="no_recipient">Kein Empfänger!</string>
    <string name="message_sending">Nachricht wird gesendet&#8230;</string>
    <string name="sent_successfully">Gesendet erfolgreich!</string>
    <string name="phone_number_warning">Bitte eine gültige Rufnummer eingeben</string>
    <string name="clean_cache">Cache löschen</string>
    <string name="site">Klinik</string>
    <string name="practice">Praxis</string>
    <string name="call_forwarding">Rufweiterleitung</string>
    <string name="answering_services">Anrufbeantworter</string>
    <string name="mobile">Handy</string>
    <string name="uploading_avatar">Anzeigebild</string>
    <string name="clean_cache_suceffuly">Cache gelöscht.</string>
    <string name="msg">MSG</string>
    <string name="page">Pager</string>
    <string name="call_office">Büro anrufen</string>
    <string name="special_skills">Spezialgebiet:</string>
    <string name="practice_location">Praxisadresse:</string>
    <string name="re">AW:</string>
    <string name="fw">WE:</string>
    <string name="reply_message">Antworten</string>
    <string name="forward_message">Weiterleiten</string>
    <string name="date">Datum:</string>
    <string name="refer_pdf">Überweisung.pdf</string>
    <string name="due">Fällig:</string>
    <string name="edit">Bearbeiten</string>
    <string name="note">Notiz:</string>
    <string name="new_task">Neue Aufgabe</string>
    <string name="edit_task">Aufgabe bearbeiten</string>
    <string name="save">Speichern</string>
    <string name="high">Hoch</string>
    <string name="med">Normal</string>
    <string name="low">Niedrig</string>
    <string name="priority">Dringlichkeit:</string>
    <string name="description">Beschreibung:</string>
    <string name="saved_successfully">Erfolgreich gespeichert!</string>
    <string name="task_done">Erledigt:</string>
    <string name="undone">offen</string>
    <string name="warning_title">Warnung!</string>
    <string name="followup_delete_warning_content">Möchten sie diese Aufgabe wirklich löschen</string>
    <string name="question_mark">\u003F</string>
    <string name="task_on">Aufgabe zu:</string>
    <string name="recipient">Empfänger:</string>
    <string name="resend">erneut versenden</string>
    <string name="new_invitation">Neue Einladung</string>
    <string name="resend_invitation">Erneut einladen</string>
    <string name="email_address">E-Mail Adresse:</string>
    <string name="input_note">Hier ergänzende Notiz eingeben (optional).</string>
    <string name="invitation_cancel_warning_message">Möchten Sie die Einladung wirklich zurücknehmen?</string>
    <string name="update_phone">Mobilgerät verwalten </string>
    <string name="update">Ändern</string>
    <string name="phone_update_info">Achtung: Die alte Nummer ist so lange aktiv, bis Sie Ihre Eingabe mit "Ändern" bestätigt haben.</string>
    <string name="phone_validate_info">Bitte validieren Sie zuerst das Mobilgerät.</string>
    <string name="mobile_phone">Handynummer:</string>
    <string name="validate_phone">Mobilgerät validieren</string>
    <string name="code_send_info">Wir haben Ihnen eine SMS mit einer PIN (Validierungscode) an Ihr Mobilgerät gesendet. Bitte geben Sie nun hier die vierstellige PIN ein.</string>
    <string name="submit">Übertragen</string>
    <string name="cannot_changed">&lt;font color=blue&gt;Die Mobilnummer wurde nicht geändert&lt;/font&gt;</string>
    <string name="error">Fehler</string>
    <string name="phone_number_warning_html">&lt;font color=blue&gt;Bitte geben sie eine gültige Nummer ein&lt;/font&gt;</string>
    <string name="code_resend_info">Falls Sie den Validierungscode nicht innerhalb von %d Minute(n) erhalten, klicken Sie bitte auf die \'erneut senden\' Schaltfläche.</string>
    <string name="cannot_new_code">Die Versuche, Ihnen einen Validierungscode zu senden, haben das Tageslimit überschritten. Haben Sie bitte Verständnis, dass wir keinen weiteren Versand mehr durchführen können. </string>
    <string name="validate_1">Den Validierungscode haben Sie noch nicht bestätigt. Bitte geben Sie zunächst den PIN-Code ein.</string>
    <string name="validate_2">Der Validierungscode ist ungültig. Bitte erneut versuchen.</string>
    <string name="validate_3">Der eingegebene Code wurde gesperrt. Bitte geben Sie den Code nach %d Stunde(n) erneut ein oder klicken Sie auf \&quot;erneut senden\&quot; um einen neuen Code zu erhalten.</string>
    <string name="validate_3_5">Der Code wurde gesperrt. Bitte geben Sie den Code nach %d Stunde(n) erneut ein .</string>
    <string name="validate_4">Der Validierungscode ist abgelaufen. Bitte fordern sie einen neuen Code an.</string>
    <string name="resend_new_code">Wir haben Ihnen einen neuen gesendet.</string>
    <string name="dissociate_warning_title">Ausloggen</string>
    <string name="dissociate_warning_message">Möchten Sie sich wirklich ausloggen? Der DoctorCom Datenspeicher auf Ihrem Mobilgerät wird dabei gelöscht!</string>

    <string-array name="invitation_options">
        <item>Ärzte zu Ihrer Praxis einladen</item>
        <item>Personal zu Ihrer Praxis einladen</item>
        <item>Fachpersonal zu Ihrer Praxis einladen</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="gcm_message">Neue Nachricht vorhanden</string>

    <plurals name="unread_messages">
        <item quantity="one">Sie haben eine neue Nachricht</item>
        <item quantity="other">Sie haben %d neue Nachrichten</item>
    </plurals>

    <string name="decrypting_file">Datei wird entschlüsselt, bitte warten&#8230;</string>
    <string name="call_my_doctorcom_number ">DoctorCom Nummer anrufen</string>
    <string name="message_body_empty">Nachrichteninhalt darf nicht leer sein!</string>
    <string name="compress_photo">Optionen zur Bildkomprimierung</string>

    <string-array name="photo_compress_item_select">
        <item>Keine Komprimierung</item>
        <item>Beste Qualität</item>
        <item>Nach Schnelligkeit</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="message_item_select">
        <item>Kopieren</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="no_mobile">Sie haben keine Mobilnummer hinterlegt!</string>
    <string name="options">Optionen</string>
    <string name="call_c2c_number">Möchten Sie die Rufnummer %s wählen?</string>
    <string name="call_from_doctorcom">Über DoctorCom anrufen</string>

    <string-array name="select_server">
        <item>United States Server</item>
        <item>Germany Server</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="select_server_dev">
        <item>United States Server</item>
        <item>Germany Server</item>
        <item>Dev Server (dev-maint)</item>
        <item>My Server</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="not_support_file_type">Dateiformat wird noch nicht unterstützt.</string>
    <string name="live_operator_backup">Live Operator Back-up</string>
    <string name="description_empty">Bitte Beschreibung ergänzen</string>
    <string name="insufficient_disk_space">Ungenügender Speicherplatz!</string>
    <string name="get_data_error_socket">{\&quot;errno\&quot;: \&quot;-1\&quot;, \&quot;descr\&quot;: \&quot;Kann keine Verbindung zum Server mit einem Socket-Verbindung Problem. Bitte versuchen Sie es erneut. !\&quot;}</string>
    <string name="invalid_url">Ungültige URL oder IP!</string>
    <string name="not_valid_server">Man kann nicht sich beim Server anmelden, weil es eine ungültige Server ist.</string>
    <string name="your_server_ip_or_domain">Ihre Server-IP oder Domain</string>
    <string name="cancelling">Abbrechen</string>
    <string name="dicom_viewer_not_ready">Der Dicom-Viewer steht Ihnen momentan nicht zur Verfügung, bitte versuchen Sie es später noch einmal.</string>
    <string name="loading_picture">Bild wird geladen&#8230;\npicture %s</string>
    <string name="dicom_study_id">Studien-ID: %s</string>
    <string name="dicom_study_description">Studien-Beschreibung: %s</string>
    <string name="dicom_series_description">Serien-Beschreibung: %s</string>
    <string name="dicom_acquisition_date">Erfassungsdatum: %s</string>
    <string name="dicom_acquisition_time">Erfassungszeit: %s</string>
    <string name="dicom_slice_location">Ort des Querschnitts: %s</string>
    <string name="dicom_patientId">Patienten ID: %s</string>
    <string name="dicom_name">Name: %s</string>
    <string name="dicom_sex">Geschlecht: %s</string>
    <string name="dicom_birthday">Geb.datum: %s</string>
    <string name="dicom_weight">Gewicht: %s</string>
    <string name="message_send_warning">Wir danken für Ihr Interesse am sicheren DoctorCom Nachrichtenversand. Die Datei wurde an den angegebenen Empfänger versendet. Um vollen Zugang zum DoctorCom Nachrichtenversand zu erhalten, müssen Sie diesen erst freischalten.</string>
    <string name="preference">Benutzereinstellungen</string>
    <string name="time_format_setting">Zeitformat</string>
    <string name="time_zone_setting">Zeitzone</string>
    <string name="h12">12-Stunden-Format</string>
    <string name="h24">24-Stunden-Format</string>
    <string name="change_timezone_warning">Die ausgewählte Zeitzone unterscheidet sich von der Zeitzone des Praxisstandortes. Möchten Sie mit dieser Einstellung fortfahren?</string>
    <string name="have_invitation">Sie haben eine Einladung erhalten</string>
    <string name="refuse">Ich lehne ab</string>
    <string name="upload_avatar">Anzeigebild</string>
    <string name="practice_organization">Praxis / Organisation</string>
    
    
    <!-- not translate yet below -->
    <string name="go_to_page">Go to Page!</string>
    <string name="load_failed_retry">Load audio file failed. Do you want to retry?</string>
    <string name="load_msg_failed_retry">Load message failed. Do you want to retry?</string>
    <string name="search_failed_retry">Search failed. Do you want to retry?</string>
    <string name="resolved">Resolved</string>
    <string name="unresolved">Unresolved</string>
    <string name="other_orgs">Other Organizations:</string>
    <string name="add_photo">Add Photo</string>
    <string name="decline_success">You have declined the invitation!</string>
    <string name="message_get_25_more">Get 25 more messages</string>
    <string name="user_get_50_more">Get 50 more users</string>
    <string name="task_get_25_more">Get 25 more tasks</string>
    <string name="get_data_error">{\&quot;errno\&quot;: \&quot;-1\&quot;, \&quot;descr\&quot;: \&quot;get data error!\&quot;}</string>
    <string name="pdf_download">PDF Download</string>
    <string name="delete">Delete</string>
    <string name="refer_address">Address:</string>
    <string name="prior_authorization_number">Prior Authorization Number:</string>
    <string name="other_authorization">Other Authorization Number:</string>
    <string name="internal_tracking_number">Internal Tracking Number:</string>
    <string name="secondary_insurance">Secondary Insurance:</string>
    <string name="secondary_insurance_id">Secondary Insurance ID:</string>
    <string name="tertiary_insurance">Tertiary Insurance:</string>
    <string name="tertiary_insurance_id">Tertiary Insurance ID:</string>
    <string name="icd_code">ICD-10 2013 code:</string>
    <string name="ops_code">OPS:</string>
    <string name="medication_list">Medication List:</string>
    <string name="notes">Refer Notes:</string>
    <string name="current_practice">Current Practice:</string>
    <string name="current_organization">Current Organization:</string>
    <string name="add_favourite">Added to Favorites!</string>
    <string name="leave_favourite">Removed from Favorites!</string>
    <string name="message_checking">Checking &#8230;</string>
    <string name="get_data_error_exception">{\&quot;errno\&quot;: \&quot;500\&quot;, \&quot;descr\&quot;: \&quot;Network anomaly.\&quot;}</string>
	<string name="start">Start</string>
	<string name="call_back_number">Callback Number:</string>
	<string name="accept_refer">Are you sure you want to accept this referral?</string>
	<string name="decline_refer">Are you sure you want to decline this referral</string>
	<string name="totally_find">Totally find</string>
    <string name="users">user(s)</string>
</resources>